in this lecture I will make my own
在这次演讲中，我将做我自己的
grunge brush and use it to make a vector
使用垃圾笔刷并使用它来创建一个矢量
sticker I will create the brush from an
贴纸我将从一个
image I go to file import I open an
图像我转到文件导入我打开一个
image with waterfalls that I downloaded
我下载的瀑布图片
from
从…
pixabay to better see the potential of
Pixabay更好地看到
the water I go to filters
我要去过滤的水
grayscale I lower the lightness I will
灰度级我会降低亮度
use the water on the left I click on the
用左边的水我点击
rectangle tool and select a piece of the
矩形工具，然后选择
water I hold shift and also select the
我按住Shift的同时也选择了
image I right click and choose set clip
图像我右击并选择设置剪辑
now I will trace the water to prevent
现在我会追踪水，以防
tracing the whole image I right click
用鼠标右键追踪整个图像
and choose crop image to clip I right
并选择裁剪图像来裁剪I右侧
click again and choose Trace bitmap to
再次单击，然后选择跟踪位图到
get the largest preview possible I will
得到尽可能大的预览，我会的
drag the trace bitmap Tab out of the tab
将轨迹位图选项卡拖出选项卡
group and I will adjust the window to
Group和我将调整窗口以
the top and bottom of my screen for
我屏幕的顶部和底部
detection mode I will choose brightness
检测模式我会选择亮度
cut off with threshold I determine how
切断门槛我决定如何
much of the water gets
大部分的水都会
white I will set threshold to 0.5 I will
白色我会将阈值设置为0.5我会
click on invert to get a black brush I
单击Invert以获得黑色画笔i
click on apply I now have a black brush
单击应用我现在有一个黑色画笔
I will call the path brush I will delete
我将把我要删除的路径命名为画笔
the
这个
image I will remove some water from the
图I将从水中移走一些水
bottom and from the side to do this I
从底部和侧面来做这件事
select the node tool I will also remove
选择我还将删除的节点工具
the nodes that are at the
位于
edges the brush is finished and I will
画笔刷完了，我会
rotate it to make it
旋转它以使其成为
horizontal now I will drag a circle I
现在水平方向，我要拖一个圆圈
will duplicate the circle twice
将重复该圆两次
I select the brush and copy it I will
我选择画笔并复制它，我会
hide two of the three circles I go to
藏起我要去的三个圆圈中的两个
path effects from the menu I choose
我从菜单中选择的路径效果
pattern along path behind pattern I
沿着图案I后面的路径的图案
choose single stretched I click on the
选择单个拉伸，我点击
paste path icon to make the brush a bit
粘贴路径图标以使画笔有点
thinner I use the edit on canvas tool I
更薄我使用在画布上编辑工具I
drag the handle in in my layers I reveal
在我显示的层中拖动手柄
the other Circle and make it a bit
另一个圆圈，让它有点
smaller to apply the effect I go to path
较小以应用我转到路径的效果
object to path to make the circle and
对象添加到路径以形成圆，并
the edge interact I shift click on the
按住Shift键单击边交互
circle then I go to path
绕圈，然后我走到小路上
exclusion now the circle in the edge or
现在排除边缘的圆圈或
a single path I will place some text I
我会在一个路径上放置一些文本，
select the text tool and click on the
选择文本工具并单击
sticker I use Grand hotel which is a
贴纸我使用Grand Hotel，这是一家
free Google font I type best to make the
免费Google字体我输入的最佳字体
text italic I can skew the text and for
文本Italic我可以倾斜文本并
the text below I will use verella round
下面的文本我将使用verella回合
which also is a free Google font to make
这也是一种免费的Google字体
the text more bold I shift click on
我点击的文本更加大胆
White at the bottom left I make the
左下角是白色，我做了
stroke
中风
smaller finally I want to add a grunge
小一点最后我想加一个垃圾
stroke I will make the last Circle a bit
中风我会把最后一个圆圈做一点
smaller and I give it a white stroke I
小一点，我给它一个白色的中风，
make the stroke thinner to get a grunge
让中风变薄以获得垃圾
stroke I use two path effects first I
中风我首先使用两个路径效应，
will choose taper stroke and then I will
我会选择锥形行程，然后我会
add roughen you can try out different
添加粗糙您可以尝试不同的
looks by clicking on the receipt icon
单击收据图标即可查看